Guide to the Leander E. Keck Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Correspondence, Series IV
  - Regarding lectures and speaking events
    - J. Balmer Showers Lectures, United Theological Seminary, Dayton, Ohio, 1983 February (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - The Illiff Week of Graduate Lectures and The Rocky Mountain Pastors' School, Denver, Colorado, 1983 January 24-27 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - First Congregational Church, Branford, Connecticut, 1983 March 20 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Ordination of John Harris Harper, 1983 June 18 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - The 26th Annual Summer Theological Conference, St. Olaf College, Northfield, Minnesota, 1983 July 18-21 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - The Congregational Church, Jacksonville, Illinois, 1983 October 23 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Mount Avery Baptist Church, Bridgeport, Connecticut, 1983 October 30 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Bishop's Seminar, United Methodist Church, Raleigh, NC, 1984 March 12-14 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Bethany Baptist Church, Newark, New Jersey, 1984 May 20 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - 1984 Bible and Theology Conference, 1984 July 9-13 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Memorial Christian Church, Midland, TX, 1985 January 6-9 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Smyth Lectures, Columbia Theological Seminary, Decatur, GA, 1985 February (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Wake Forest Spring Conference, Wake Forest University, Winston-Salem, North Carolina, 1985 March 18-19 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Duke University Chapel, Durham, North Carolina, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Old Presbyterian Meeting House, Alexandria, Virginia, 1986 May 4 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - The H. Allen Atwood Memorial Lectures, First United Methodist Church, Janesboro, Arkansas, 1985 October 13-15 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - The First Congregational Church of Darian, Darian, CT, 1985 November 3 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - TCU Ministers Week, McFadin Lecturer, Fort Worth, TX, 1986 February 3-6 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Cotner College Lectureship, Lincoln, Nebraska, 1986 March 12 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - The First Congregational Church, Old Lyme, Connecticut, 1986 April 20 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Eden Theological Seminary, St. Louis, MO, 1986 April 30 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - First Congregational Church, Old Greenwich, CT, 1986 September 26-28 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - First Congregational Church, New Milford, CT, 1986 October 5 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - SMU, Dallas, TX, 1986 October 10-11 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - New Haven Association of United Church of Christ, 1986 October 23 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Fifth Annual Dr. Lloyd H. Rising Theological Lecture, "Paul: Problem and Promise", First Methodist Church, Pittsburg, Kansas, 1987 October 21 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - "Jesus and Christology", Florida Southern College, 1988 February 4 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - New Directions in Biblical Studies, 20th Atlantic Seminar in Theological Education, Truro, Nova Scotia, 1988 June 5-10 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Sermon - Congregation Church of Brookfield, 1988 October 30 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - First Congregational Church of Ringfield, 1989 January 29 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Wabash College Commencement, 1994 May (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - World Methodist Council, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Confessing Christ Craigville Center for "Joyous Theological Reflection and Serious Theological Work", 1994 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Northern Baptist Seminary, 1994 October 4 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - "Who is Jesus?", The 57th Annual Mid-Winter Convocation, Luther Seminary, 1995 January 4-6 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Clark Lectures - Duke, 1995 March (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Evangelism Congress, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - SMU, 1996 March (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Hall Lecture, University of South Carolina, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Mixed Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Regarding publications/ with publishers
    - Abingdon Press - Interpreter's One-Volume Commentary correspondence, 1959-1970 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Hadden House - Association Press Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Abingdon Press - Schubert Festschrift, 1960s (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Harper's Correspondence, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Association Press, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - JBL, New Testament Studies, Harvard Theological Review - "The Spirit and the Dove" correspondence, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Fortress Press - Royalties and Misc, 1970-1980 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Abingdon Press - Future for the Historical Jesus Correspondence, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - TRE Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Fortress Press correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Christian Boards of Publication correspondence, 1973-1985 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Oxford Press - Literary Forms of the Bible, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Abingdon Press - Korean translation of A Future for The Historical Jesus, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Fortress Press - Proclamation Series, 1974-1979 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Fortress Press - Pentecost, 1975-1975 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Interpretation, 1975-1979 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Abingdon Press, 1975-1980 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Fortress Press - Misc., 1975-1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Anchor Bible - Romans, 1975-1992 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Oxford University Press - The New English Bible, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Bethany Press and Christian, 1976-1983 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Adult Publications, Adult Leader, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Trinity University Press - Folklore Studies and the Gospels, 1977-1978 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Fortress Press - Proclamation Series, Paul: Contract, etc, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Bible in the Pulpit, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Fortress Press - Proclamation II, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Fortress Press - Proclamation Holy Week, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Judson Press - Mandate to Witness, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Loyola - Ethos and Ethics in the N.T., 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Abingdon Press - Taking the Bible Seriously, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Fortress Press - Studies in Luke-Acts, 1978-1979 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Abingdon - Interpretation The Pauline Letters, 1978-1989 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Fortress Press - Paul and His Letters, 1978-1991 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Abingdon Press - Articles for Abingdon Dictionary of Living Religions, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Doubleday Press, 1979-1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Homiletic Journal, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Fortress Press - Paul and His Letters, Italian edition, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Fortress Press - Proclamation Pentecost II, 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Fortress Press - Future of the Historical Jesus, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Abingdon Press - Taking the Bible Seriously, 1981-1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Abingdon - Misc., 1981-1989 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Circuit Rider, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - CBP Press - The N.T. Experience of Faith, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Macmillan Publishing Co., 1983 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Mercer Press, 1983-1987 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Interpretation - various articles, Editorial Council, 1980-1987 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Abingdon - Bible in the Pulpit, 1987, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Fortress Press -Essays, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Exodus Press, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Fortress Press - General, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Scholars Press - Religion and Theology Scholarship Series, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Abingdon Press -N.I.B. (The New Interpreter's Bible), 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Fortress Press and others - Wayne Meeks' Festschrift, 1991-1995 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Augsburg Fortress - What makes Romans Tick? SBL, 1992 November, revised 1994 August (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - United Methodist Publishing House, 1994 October (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Interpretation - Sprunt Lectures, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Abingdon Press - Romans Commentary, 1996-1998 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Abingdon Press - Jesus in the Gospel (Contract), 2002 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Chronological sequence
    - Paul Schubert re. dissertation; Wellesley College position, 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Vanderbilt University, 1959-1971 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Postdoctoral research, summer research grants, 1964-1971 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Society of Biblical Literature, 1968-1972 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Sabbatical, teaching at Union Theological Seminary, Philippines, Cambridge, 1969-1971 (Box 23, Folder 9a)
    - Emory University, 1972-1979 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Society for Scripture and Tradition, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - James H. Charlesworth, 1974-1982 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Colloquy on Gospels, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Responses to Speech at Kansas City Apocalypse and Ecclesia, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Religious Studies Review II, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1975, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Robert Jewett, 1975-1987 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Antioch Group, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Ernst Kasemann, 1976-1979 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Wiley vs. Franklin, 1978-1979 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Blasphemy accusations, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Yale Divinity School, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Social World of Early Christianity, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Association of Theological Schools, 1980s (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - New Haven Theological Discussion Group, 1980-1991 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - D. Moody Smith, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Lutheran Diaspora, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Christian Church in NC, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, including regarding Keck family genealogy, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Asbury Theological Seminary, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - SBL Pauline Theology Consultation, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Quarterly Review Editorial Board, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Perkins School of Theology - Board of Visitors, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Sabbatical in Cambridge, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, including with Gene Outka, Benno Schmidt, 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Automobile accident, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Disciple consultation, 1992-1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Stalcup Lecture, Dallas - cancelation, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - International Center for Interfaith Organizations, 1992-1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Emory University invitation, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Biographical Documentation, Series V
  - Curriculum vitae, 2013, no date (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - "Intellectual History" presented to New Haven Theological Group, 1989 Mar 17 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Who's Who in America and other directory biographical entries, 1973-1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1975-1995 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Awards, tributes, memorabilia, 1955-2007 (Box 25, Folder 12)